export default [
    {
        lesson: 1,
        quizItems:[
            {
                id: 1,
                slug: 'question_1',
                question: 'First Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'First anwer',
                    2: 'Second anwer',
                    3: 'Third anwer',
                    4: 'Fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 3,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 2,
                slug: 'question_2',
                question: 'Second Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Second Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Second Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Second Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Second Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 2,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 3,
                slug: 'question_3',
                question: 'Third Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Second Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Second Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Second Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Second Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 1,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 4,
                slug: 'question_4',
                question: 'Please write the name of capital of bangladesh',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Rajshahi',
                    2: 'Dhaka',
                    3: 'Kumilla',
                    4: 'Jamalpur',
                },
                currectAnswer: 2,
                answerType: 'text',
            },
            {
                id: 5,
                slug: 'question_5',
                question: 'Fifth Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Three anwer',
                    2: 'Four anwer',
                    3: 'Two anwer',
                    4: 'One anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: [4,3,1,2],
                answerType: 'drag',
            },
            {
                id: 6,
                slug: 'question_6',
                question: 'Sixth Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Sixth Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Sixth Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Sixth Question third anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: [1, 3],
                answerType: 'multiple options',
            },
            {
                id: 7,
                slug: 'question_7',
                question: 'Seventh Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Sixth Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Sixth Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Sixth Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Sixth Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 3,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 8,
                slug: 'question_8',
                question: 'Eighth Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Eighth Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Eighth Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Eighth Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Eighth Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 4,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 9,
                slug: 'question_9',
                question: 'Sixth Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Sixth Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Sixth Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Sixth Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Sixth Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 1,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 10,
                slug: 'question_10',
                question: 'Sixth Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Sixth Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Sixth Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Sixth Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Sixth Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: [2, 3],
                answerType: 'multiple options',
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        lesson: 2,
        quizItems:[
            {
                id: 1,
                slug: 'question_1',
                question: 'First Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'First anwer',
                    2: 'Second anwer',
                    3: 'Third anwer',
                    4: 'Fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 3,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 2,
                slug: 'question_2',
                question: 'Second Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Second Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Second Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Second Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Second Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 2,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 3,
                slug: 'question_3',
                question: 'Third Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Second Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Second Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Second Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Second Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 1,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 4,
                slug: 'question_4',
                question: 'Please write the name of capital of bangladesh',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Rajshahi',
                    2: 'Dhaka',
                    3: 'Kumilla',
                    4: 'Jamalpur',
                },
                currectAnswer: 2,
                answerType: 'text',
            },
            {
                id: 5,
                slug: 'question_5',
                question: 'Fifth Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Three anwer',
                    2: 'Four anwer',
                    3: 'Two anwer',
                    4: 'One anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: [4,3,1,2],
                answerType: 'drag',
            },
            {
                id: 6,
                slug: 'question_6',
                question: 'Sixth Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Sixth Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Sixth Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Sixth Question third anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: [1, 3],
                answerType: 'multiple options',
            },
            {
                id: 7,
                slug: 'question_7',
                question: 'Seventh Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Sixth Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Sixth Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Sixth Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Sixth Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 3,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 8,
                slug: 'question_8',
                question: 'Eighth Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Eighth Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Eighth Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Eighth Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Eighth Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 4,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 9,
                slug: 'question_9',
                question: 'Sixth Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Sixth Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Sixth Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Sixth Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Sixth Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: 1,
                answerType: 'single option',
            },
            {
                id: 10,
                slug: 'question_10',
                question: 'Sixth Question will here',
                answers: {
                    1: 'Sixth Question first anwer',
                    2: 'Sixth Question second anwer',
                    3: 'Sixth Question third anwer',
                    4: 'Sixth Question fourth anwer',
                },
                currectAnswer: [2, 3],
                answerType: 'multiple options',
            }
        ]
    }
]